Evgen Vittsenko

Frontend Developer

Contacts

Ukraine (remote)

+380678043844

GitHub

in www.linkedin.com

@EvgenVittsenko

Tech Skills

- HTML | CSS | SCSS
- BEM | Adaptive & responsive web desing
- Flexbox | Grid layuot
- **JavaScript**, TypeScript
- Vue.js | Nuxt.js
- Vuex | Pinia
- Vue router | Vuetify
- Vue CLI, Vite
- ESLint
- Rest API | Fetch | Axios
- Git, GitLab | Figma | VS code | Webstorm
- Linux, Jira, Trello
- Webflow

Soft Skills

- Developed sense of responsibility, self organization
- Good analytical and communication skills
- Frankness

Education

Participant of the mentoring program from Beetroot Academy

Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

Beetroot Academy Front-End Developing

Jun 2022 - Nov 2022

Zaporizhzhia National Technical University

Faculty of transport, Organization of transportation

Languages

Ukrainian: Native

English: Pre-Intermediate (A2)

Summary

I have almost 2 years of commercial experience in Frontend development, during which I have worked extensively with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Vue.js/Nuxt.js framework. I specialise in developing projects of various sizes, focusing on creating new landing pages and components, implementing the necessary logic and functionality, and working with existing codebases. I have experience in all stages of the development lifecycle, from initial design to final deployment. In my chosen field, I find inspiration in the opportunity to continually develop and refine my skills, ultimately aiming to deliver maximum value to the business.

Portfolio

Link to my portfolio-site:

https://yevhen0905.github.io/portfolio/

Professional Experience

Frontend Developer at DDI Development

June 2024 - present

Key responsibilities:

- development of new components on the project, work with the existing code base, adaptive layout
- creating new product functionality and features using Vue.js
- fix bugs, code refactoring, optimization
- collaborate with various functional departments to deliver client solutions, from initial discussions to implementation

Frontend Developer at UNIMO

Aug 2023 - April 2024

Key responsibilities:

- development of new landing pages, editing, adaptive layout
- creating new features and capabilities on the site using Vue.js,
 Nuxt.js
- fix bugs, code refactoring, optimization
- collaborating with developers, Ui/Ux designer

Frontend Developer, Self-employed

Mar 2023 - July 2023

Leading specialist, Logistics manager

"ADMIRAL LOGISTICS" LLC,
"ASKO EXPEDITION" LLC,
ZAZ Automobile Plant

Key responsibilities as a logistician:

- planning of international transportation, introduction of negotiations
- full information support of all transport processes
- document flow control, conclusion of contracts

Acquired skills:

- Experience of working in both large and relatively small teams..
- The ability to work with a large amount of information and to complete tasks in a stipulated time
- Planning work processes